# **Yash Chouhan**

## React Native Developer

yash18chouhan@gmail.com

**&** 8146789775

• Chandigarh, India

github.com/uniqueyash18

#### **EDUCATION**

# B Tech in Computer Science and Engineering,

Institute of engineering and technology 11/2020 – 06/2023

Percentage :- 8 CGPA

Diploma in Computer Science and engineering, Chandigarh college of engineering and technology 08/2017 – 06/2020 Percentage: - 7.5 CGPA

#### Matriculation,

Bal Niketan Model sr sec School, 04/2017

Percentage: - 9.4 CGPA

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

Communication

**Problem-solving** 

**Adaptability** 

**Teamwork** 

Leadership

### **CERTIFICATES**

# Diploma in Software Application and Data Processing

National Institute of Computer Technology

# Python with Data Science and Machine Learning

**NIELET** 

#### AWARDS

Brewer Of The Week, CodeBrew Labs 
Recognized as "Brewer of the Week" at
Code Brew Labs for exemplary
dedication, innovation, and leadership in
React Native development and support.

#### PROFILE

As a React Native Developer, I bring technical expertise and leadership to drive innovation and deliver exceptional mobile experiences. With a strong track record in support operations and client satisfaction, I excel in collaborative environments, leveraging my development, communication, and problem-solving skills to achieve and surpass organizational goals. My proficiency in React Native, TypeScript, CSS, Node.js, JavaScript, HTML, and React.js ensures the delivery of top-tier solutions.

## PROFESSIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE

**Codebrew Labs,** React Native Developer ☑ 01/2023 – present

- Led a team of 4 training developers in support operations, optimizing processes.
- Implemented Video Chat and Chat Modules with agorarn-uikit and socket.io, and managed caching with React Query/TanStack Query.
- Live Tracking Modules- React Native Maps and MapView Direction.

#### Meander Software, React is 🛮

10/2022 - 12/2022

- Developed and maintained web applications using React.js.
- Collaborated with senior developers to implement UI components and optimize performance.
- Gained hands-on experience with JavaScript, HTML, and CSS in creating responsive web applications.

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

### Front End Development — React

Native | Node.js | Redux | MMKV | TanStack

Query | Axios | AgoraUI kit **Programming Languages** —

JavaScript | TypeScript • **Web Development** — React.js

| HTML | CSS

#### PROJECTS

#### Roash Deals App,

Marketing Solution for E-Commerce Brands ☑

**Royo Product,** Developed multi-module application. Integrated chat sockets and payment gateways including Stripe. ☑

**Qdelo,** Food Delivery Solution: Implemented a coupon-based platform for live coupons; integrated sockets for real-time updates. ☑

**Tilalre,** Real Estate Solution: Implemented group chat and one-to-one chat functionalities for enhanced communication.